Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy & Personal Data Protection Policy!

Privacy Policy

Privacy & Personal Data Protection Policy!
------------------------------------------

Privacy Policy – GDPR
---------------------

Our privacy policies and practices focus on the processing, sharing, and storage of personal information appropriately and lawfully, while providing privacy, integrity, and availability.

Personal data protection policy in accordance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016:

Date of publication: 01 June 2021

Who we are
----------

iZi Media is a private Greek – Bulgarian web design company, which was founded in Varna, Bulgaria, and has a market share in the construction of web pages and web applications. iZi Media is a subsidiary of iZi Media Group. For more information about the activities of our company please visit the link: [https://izimedia.gr/](https://izimedia.gr/en/)

Where we belong
---------------

iZi Media is registered with the General European Chamber.

Authorities
-----------

iZi Media data protection policy is based on the following data protection principles:

* The processing of personal data takes place in a legal, fair, and transparent manner;
* The collection of personal data will only take place for specified, clear, and lawful purposes and will not be further processed in a way that is incompatible with those purposes;
* The collection of personal data will be sufficient, relevant, and limited to that which is necessary for relation to the purpose for which it is processed;
* Personal data should be accurate and, where necessary, up to date;
* Every reasonable step should be taken to ensure that personal data that is inaccurate for the purposes for which it is processed, deleted, or corrected without delay;
* Personal data should be kept in a format that allows the data subject to be identified for no more than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data is processed;
* All personal data will be kept confidential and stored in a manner that ensures proper security;
* Personal data will not be shared with third parties except when necessary to provide services to them by agreement;  
    Data subjects will have the right to request access to and correction or deletion of personal data, or restriction on processing, or an objection to the processing as well as the right to data portability.

Personal data
-------------

Personal data means any information that may be relevant to an identified or unidentifiable natural person (the “data subject”). Personal data includes all types of information that are direct or indirect (that is, used in conjunction with other data) attributable to the data subject, such as names, date of birth, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, etc.

Collection of personal data
---------------------------

Website users who wish to take advantage of our services and submit information to us may be required to provide personal data to enable iZi Media to operate and improve our company and our services. We primarily collect personal data such as names, telephone numbers, email addresses, to communicate with our customers.

Use of personal data
--------------------

We will use personal data for the purpose for which it is collected, and will retain the data only for as long as it is necessary for that purpose. Access to personal data is severely restricted to iZi Media staff and its affiliated affiliates and affiliates who are properly certified and have a clear corporate need for data.

Use of Cookies
--------------

The website of iZi Media and its affiliates, iZi Media Group uses cookies or similar technologies to ensure an excellent user experience and to analyze trends, to manage the website, monitor the movements of users throughout the website, and gather demographic information relevant to our user base as a whole. Cookies are small text files placed on a user’s device to monitor usage patterns and registration preferences. Our cookies do not contain information that can identify individuals. We collect certain information automatically through the use of cookies and tracking technologies such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referral/login pages, files displayed on our page (e.g. HTML pages, graphics), operating systems, date/time imprint, and/or browsing data to analyze trends overall and to manage the page. Website users may control the use of cookies at the level of the private browser but if users choose to disable cookies, this may restrict the use of certain features or functions on our website or our services.

Personal data sharing
---------------------

Personal data should not be shared with third parties except in circumstances where such sharing is necessary for the provision of our services.

In certain circumstances, you may be required to disclose personal information in response to legitimate requests from supervisors to meet GDPR requirements. We may also disclose personal information if required by law, as well as comply with a summons or other legal proceedings, where we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, to protect the safety of our customers, or the safety of others, to investigate fraud, or to respond to a government request.

Processing security
-------------------

We will process personal data securely, implement and maintain proper technical and organizational measures to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure, or access, especially where the processing involves the transfer of data through a network, and against all other illegal forms of processing.

E-mail marketing
----------------

iZi Media is allowed to send e-mails to customers by consent. The specific form of consent must be given freely, be specifically informed, and be clear. These prerequisites are met when customers have chosen to receive email marketing (actively agreeing).

Customers will always have the right to object, upon request and at no cost, to the processing of personal customer-related data for the purpose of direct marketing activities without having to provide a specific justification. Customers can do this using the “Unsubscribe” link which they will find in the e-mails they receive from us or by contacting us at [info@izimedia.gr.](mailto:info@izimedia.gr) Once a customer has disagreed, that customer’s personal data will no longer be processed for direct marketing.

Email marketing contains information that we believe may be of interest to our customers, such as the latest news about our products and services.

Responsibility
--------------

iZi Media as well as iZi Media Group is responsible and wants to be able at any given time to demonstrate compliance with the GDPR as well as with our principles set out here. iZi Media will maintain records of processing activities under its responsibility that contain the information required by the GDPR and where applicable and will make the files available to supervisors upon request.

Complaints
----------

Customers have the right to make a complaint regarding the processing of our personal data.

In the unlikely event that customers are harmed by a breach of their data protection rights and iZi Media has not responded to the complaint adequately, customers can formally complain to supervisors.

Changes to this policy
----------------------

This policy may be renewed from time to time, e.g. due to changes in the relevant legislation or changes in the corporate structure of iZi Media. If any material changes are made, customers will be notified via email or via a notice on the website before the change becomes effective. We encourage all our users to periodically check this page for the latest information on privacy practices.

### Navigation

### Useful Links

### Free Consultation

### Follow Us on Social Media



#### Phone



#### Email



#### Address

© 2021 – iZi Media – iZi Media Group | Design and Hosting by **[izimedia.gr](https://izimedia.gr/)** and **[izihost.io](https://izihost.io/)** | All Rights Reserved ©℗®™
